See, Namahai Singer.
Yes, sir.
Yes, it's the other way around.
It's the other way around.
Yes, and Amehiko-sama...
He's got horns!
Please, please, please...
Yes, please.
What?
What the...!
Oh!
No!
Hey, look!
Thank you for watching!
It's been a long time!
Yes, it's been a while! Please do!
And I am a yellow clunky fresh fool. Please take care of me when I change my name again.
So, I would like to continue with this week's edition.
Well, it's been windy lately, hasn't it?
Yes, it has been.
Wasn't it strong last night?
It was terrible.
It was like a boom at first.
Then the wind hit the window and boom, boom, boom.
I'll be very happy tomorrow.
Oh, really?
I wonder what's going on, is the wind god mad at me?
Oh, Subie.
Sure thing.
Subie-subie.
Subie-subie-subie.
Subie, you're so sparkly.
Now, I'm in the first year of high school.
First year of high school, huh, but not yet.
Yes.
But, I see. So you were in the eighth grade when you first met?
Eighth grade, yes.
I was in the eighth grade.
That's right.
And now you are in high school.
You've become a replayer.
That's right.
My academic ability hasn't improved at all.
It's going up a little.
I'm getting a little bit better.
So, I'm going to be a little bit more solemn about the recording.
What a hot topic.
There was one hot topic.
I've got something to tell you.
How, I'm doing a program on TVK, and I'm often a guest or something at this museum's debut.
L.O.L. will be holding an event on Saturday, May 6, at the museum hall.
The title of the event is "Secret Settlement L.O.L. Planets Shareholders' Meeting.
I was told that there will be an event titled "Secret Settlement L.O.L. Planets Shareholders Meeting.
And I was invited as a guest.
Master.
I'm also a shareholder.
As a shareholder.
As a shareholder. I don't know.
I don't have one, but as a shareholder.
I'd like to take part in the meeting.
If you have a few minutes, please come and join us.
Doors open at 3:00 p.m., the show starts at 4:00 p.m., and the show will end at 6:00 p.m.
The show will end at 6:00 p.m.
Yes, that's right.
So, please come and join us.
Yes.
So, the Secret Settlement L.O.L. Planets Shareholders' Meeting.
Oh! Wait a minute.
Wait a minute for the title.
Secret Settlement L.O.L. Planets Shareholders' Meeting.
Supportive by Overaging.
Oh!
Talk like I'm paying for it.
Cool!
I'll pay for it.
Like the cost of renting a hall.
Like a savings account.
Master, the way to pay for it is free of charge.
I'll pay for the proposed viewing.
It's free of charge for everyone!
It's nice to have free admission, isn't it?
Once again, prices are getting higher these days, and we live in an age where we can't even buy eggs.
Prices are strong, aren't they? I mean, there was the Sobey flu and all.
If you have time, it's free of charge.
Saturday!
I, too, have not been informed of what we are going to do at all.
I guess they just want me to give them the money.
I was told it would be an item-assault.
I said it's ok, and it's done! And that was it.
And that was it.
That was it.
Then I went to support and they said it was over.
Please give us this notice today. That was the second thing he said.
That's great.
Well, well, well... I think I can do a lot of things in LOL-chan.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
So, I guess I'll go and do the recording of the program.
Yes, so today is another start. This is my debut in the cold.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Fun, fun, fun.
A fun coffee shop!
Yay!
Thank you!
That's what I meant,
Yes.
Anyway, this week is the week when we get a lot of big stools.
Oh, wow.
Thank you very much.
For example, when you go to the beach..,
Yes.
Fishermen catch a lot of fish,
There are times when there are no fish at all, even if they are fishing in the same place,
Yes, that's right.
I can understand how fishermen feel.
You just sent me an e-mail.
I understand.
We have a lot of fish this week!
Thank you very much.
What's going on, guys!
No, no, no,
Was there some kind of free or something campaign?
Oh, yeah, there was.
Like, if you send an email to us on your cold-weather debut, we'll give you 1,000 yen kickback now.
Wow, that's great.
That's pretty good.
Very good.
That's great.
Well, if that's the case, I'll probably pay for everything.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes.
So, as long as you can spare the time,
I would like to read a little bit.
Yes, I'd like to read it.
Let's see, first of all,
I'd like to start off with a little bit of...
Noodle.
Mensha.
Ramen noodles.
Yes, yes, yes.
Mensha.
Mr. Suginami-ku, Tokyo Night Commuter Express.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
I'm a little bit sick to my stomach,
Yes.
I was wondering if you would like to eat noodles at that time,
I also received such a thing.
Yes.
Genius master!
Yes, sir.
Mr. Subie, the Noodle Noodle Ebi Chu!
Brother Ryan, the handsome clunker!
Good evening!
By the way, Master, is the transformation belt around your waist spinning these days?
I used to get so sick to my stomach that I had to use the masked Haliter character's belt to transform myself into a diarrhea shocker.
I used to get sick to my stomach so much that I used to do a character called "Masked Haliter" who was called "Diarrhea Shocker".
No! I hate it! I'm filthy!
This is real! It's not dirty!
Everybody's going there! People are walking, people are flowing!
All the time, all the time!
Please don't say that.
I said it.
I was in the middle of the night the other night, transforming belts into masked hariters.
I had a hard time because the windmill kept spinning.
The next day I had a figure meal of something digestible.
Oh, I heard that you probably went to Nagasaki on a business trip
I bought it as a souvenir at Nagasaki Airport.
Hand-pulled milk noodles
Thin noodles in a light broth of sago soup
Thin noodles with a light broth of sago broth
It healed my body from the diarrhea shocker!
Wow! Looks delicious!
It's good, isn't it?
Aago dashi soup stock!
Aago dashi is a culture of Kyushu, especially Nagasaki, isn't it?
Well, you know what "aago dashi" is, don't you?
Not this one, by the way.
That's it! I thought it was bonito giblets?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, it's kinda like that.
This, this, this is not the chin.
It's pretty far forward.
There you go!
What is that?
Well, you're right.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm getting nervous.
Oh, dried fish?
Quiet a minute.
I can't edit this in the live feed.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh, goo.
Ago?
"Go" is their word for "fish".
Yes, yes, I just saw it.
What?
I saw it.
I saw it... Did you send it to me?
Flying fish. Flying fish.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What a modern society! Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
You mean I can cheat legally.
Thank you very much.
Well, you know, there are a lot of tobios over there.
I'm the guy who did it... and the ramen is like that too...
It's really good!
You won't forget it after one more drink!
What the heck! It's like...
I want to try it!
Of course the dried sardines are good, but
But it's more, it's kind of refreshing.
I mean, it's light, but...
And yet...
But at the same time, it has a richness to it, like it's well seasoned.
Maybe you have a chance to go to Ebichu? You know, the culture there, Nagasaki, Saka...
I know, when I went to Fukuoka, I only had tonkotsu (pork bone) soup.
Of course tonkotsu is delicious, but there are also ramen noodles made with "akodashi" and there are many other ramen restaurants that use "akodashi" as well.
It's a part of their culture, I guess. I'm going on a tour.
By the way, I got some photos from them, and here they are.
Enobe nyumen. Looks delicious!
It's a little bit like somen noodles... but the soup is clear.
This soup is clear, but it's a beautiful soup!
After eating this, we all look like Mr. Inoki!
Because it's a chin
It's a hood, so it's gentle, but it's infused.
And Mr. Pell from Yokohama City, he often sends us great pictures.
Thank you very much, Master Rhea.
This time I photographed the moon with a telephoto camera.
It's the 23rd day after the new moon.
The waxing moon.
May I? First.
Let's see.
Oh, wait a minute.
Sometimes it doesn't download.
Sorry about that.
Improve this now!
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go!
Oh!
Beautiful!
The crater is well captured!
You can get this good a shot with a telephoto lens on a camera.
Amazing!
I've seen pictures of this place on a specialist's table or something.
It's true.
It's beautiful.
It's amazing.
Beautiful.
I wonder what kind of millimeter he used.
The bottom.
I'm sure you'll notice that.
I'm sure you'll be able to find a way to get a good look at the newest addition to the lineup.
Master Visual Good evening Devil and Mr. Rhea how do you do?
Yora Nakamura came to work with us last week.
Last week, Yora Nakamura came to work for us... and I thought it would be cuter if she just said "balicata" instead of posing for us.
When I said "balicata" when I did the stairs with the eyes, everyone was like, "Wow! Wow!
She's so cute. She's so cute.
Wow!
They were like, "Wow!
I immediately drew a picture of that pose.
It's like this.
Wow, it's so cute!
You've got it right, you've got it right, you've got it right, you've got it right, you've got it right, you've got it right.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
The tulips in the park were beautiful.
Yay, yay, beautiful! Look at the calendar! It's spring!
Wow, I didn't know you could take such beautiful pictures.
I wonder if this was taken with a cell phone.
If it's a cell phone, it's true.
It's like, "Oh my God, it's already May." Amazing.
It's so beautiful.
Wait a minute...
Ms. Hanabibito and Ms. Sue, from Shizuoka, a company employee, e-mailing for the first time...
She made a miniature of the signboard that you see on the front of the museum, you know, the one with the "shiny lights" on it.
What?
He made it. So cute!
The one with the batteries in it...
Geezer, I'm sorry to interrupt, but before that... no news.
Good evening. Thank you for your always entertaining and informative show.
I made a cute Devil sign in the museum by remodeling a miniature sign sold at 100-yen stores.
I'm looking forward to next year's show as well, and I'm looking forward to a long and loose show in the future.
I thought I was doing it loosely, I thought I was doing it beautifully.
I've got it right here.
It's in the case.
Is this it?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So...
A sign.
Yes, yes, yes.Yes, sir.
First of all...
Yes, sir.
It's like this. It's so cute!
Wow! Cute!
Yes! Amazing!
It looks like this!
Wow! It's so cute!
Even the smallest details have been reproduced in great detail!
By the way, this thing turns on electricity!
Oh, my gosh! Can I?
Please! May I?
Switch on!
Yay! We're open for business!
So cute!
The light's a little bluish.
It's so realistic. Amazing.
It's so cute!
Thank you very much. We got a lot of these.
If you guys don't mind...
I'm so happy! You don't mind? Here you go.
Thank you very much! Thank you, Suu!
Thank you very much!
By the way, this Mr. Suu, it says "Suveyoshi" on it.
Ah! Yes!
That's right. Thank you very much.
Do you know him?
Yes! Yes, I know her!
We had a free live concert, and you came to the benefit party, too.
Oh, my God! Mr. Suu!
Thank you so much!
He's quite a guy, isn't he?
He's so cute! He's so cute!
Well, well, well... That's how it goes.
And, uh...
Well, you know, he also put batteries in it.
What? Why?
I probably got the title elsewhere, so I'll give it to you later, and the batteries too.
Thank you very much.
Oh, you're so kind.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Amazing.
So cute.
Wow, some people are asking to borrow some goods.
Cute, even if it's at home, it's cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
When I'm working on my computer, if this shines like this, I can't help but look at it.
I'm going to put it on my desk.
Thank you very much.
Here we go. So, I put it out, and then, you know...
Mr. Yoshio from Yamanashi Prefectural Public Relations Magazine.
Yes.
Let's see, you are the very genius master, Subie-sama of Ebichu, the cute little shrimp.
I'll be happy to see you, Mr. Raiya, a regular customer.
I'll try to be happy.
Maybe it's already the season of fresh green plum blossoms here, but it is the season,
I heard that there are still some places in Yamanashi where you can see cherry blossoms,
The other day, I guided an acquaintance from Osaka to this place, and he saw it,
The other day, I took an acquaintance from Osaka to see the cherry blossoms, and he said, "This is the original landscape of Yamanashi, or rather, of Japan.
He is from the Kansai region.
Yes.
I am from my hometown, so I was just curious about it,
I told him that I would send him a photo of what might be the original landscape.
I'll send you a picture of what might be the original scenery.
So, I did.
Oh, wow.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Amazing.
It's definitely a little bit like this, I wonder what it is.
It's made the old-fashioned way.
The building looks like it was built in the olden days.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Wow, there are still so many cherry blossoms.
How nice!
I didn't get to see cherry blossoms this year.
You couldn't?
Oh no.
I'm sorry, Lia. What is it?
Last week, I saw a picture of you saying that you had cherry blossom viewing.
And, well, everyone had a great time today.
What's that?
A touch of horse touch!
Touching? I was horse-touched.
Ma Xiaochi is the name of a general in the "Romance of the Three Kingdoms",
He was a subordinate of Zhuge Xiaoming, who was an excellent man,
He was an excellent man, but he committed a violation of military law.
He was a very talented man, but he committed a slight violation of military law, and was severely cut down.
There is a famous Chinese saying from the "Three Kingdoms" that says, "Crying is cutting a horse's tentacles,
In "Kanrai Devil," he cried because he had no choice but to do so, and he was told that he had to cut out the material.
I see.
Do you want to see it now? Are you sure?
Won't it be cut again?
That's right, he said he was touched by a touch of a touch of a touch.
Wouldn't that be double-touching?
I have to say "touchy-feely".
I think that you are going to do devils' work in the future,
I think that, you know, if you continue to work on Devil, the photos and stories you introduce will be very popular, and you will do it in Chugoku Rokku,
And then, when the show goes on the air....
There's not a shadow of him!
This is a cold Devil's term, "horse touch".
I hope you remember it.
I experienced my first touch of the horse.
By the way, here is a picture of Rhea, who was touched by the horse touch, at a cherry blossom viewing.
It's great!
The photo is great and so is his partner!
But the scale!
The scale is right, isn't it?
The scale is the scale!
There's so much going on, you know.
I can't help it.
But it's in full bloom.
That's right.
I was given this place in Saitama prefecture,
I was happy and I was able to see the flowers with my partner here.
My partner and I had a cherry blossom viewing party here.
I was wondering if you are a comedian with this girl.
No, no, no. I thought you were a comedian? Maybe you mean yourself?
I thought you were a comic, but you didn't make it to the semifinals of M-1, did you?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, not at all.
I dance and sing.
He and I have a comic group called 66.
Oh, that's not a comic group,
It's not a comic, it's a rock-rock group.
That's all right.
What's so strange is that I'm used to seeing Raiya-kun in the audience,
You look so serious, but you don't look like you're in any hurry at all.
No, you can see it, can't you?
The truth is, I'm the negative one and he's the positive one.
Wow!
He talks a lot.
He does make V-signs and stuff like that.
That's right.
It's so casual.
That's right. He has more friends than me and talks more than me.
Oh, surprisingly, yes.
Yes.
It's hard to tell at a glance, really.
Hey, Kataya, you got carried away with the takoyaki.
No, they were delicious.
They were delicious, these takoyaki.
Looks delicious.
He really likes takoyaki.
You don't understand.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, you know, there are things like this.
Well, you all sent us lots of pictures of cherry blossoms and cherry blossom viewing, didn't you?
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Well, I think it's next year again in terms of timing.
Yes, I think it will be next year.
By all means.
Oh, that's right. And I'm afraid that I may be abused after this.
I'd like to tell you this only for those who are watching the live broadcast.
Various people have asked me to write a song about Mt.
Yes, yes, yes.
I've been asked by many people to write a song about Mt.
And, well, you know, the famous Mt.
Fuji.
Fuji, so I decided not to call him by his name, so I called him Mr. Fuji.
When I was making a song about Mr. Fuji, I went to film him.
Well, of course, I went there to take pictures, and I have some photos of the past.
Yes, I did.
If you have any good pictures of Mt. Fuji that you would like to share with us, please let us know.
Oh.
Fuji, please send them to me. Well, you know, if you send me a lot of pictures, I may not be able to include some of them.
I would like to work with you all as much as possible in making a song about Mt.
I may have one too.
Oh!
I went to see Diamond Fuji.
What!
I went to see it when I was little, with my family.
I might have a picture of it.
Oh, then, by all means, let's, uh, see there.
Yes.
Like a suvie.
Yes, that's right.
It might appear.
So, by all means, I usually receive a lot of photos of Mt.
Fuji's pictures.
But, I'm not so good at it, so I'm going to send this picture again.
If you have any more, please send them to the e-mail form.
If you have any questions, please feel free to send them to the e-mail form.
So, I'm gone now.
Yes, I did.
Well, it all happened very quickly.
Yes.
How was it?
Well, you already gave us another picture of the cherry blossom viewing, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I feel like I'm going to get abused by everyone again.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You know what I mean!
I understand. I can feel it in the air.
You know, I, I, I, I, I am probably the most abused person in Kanri Devil.
Oh, really?
Of course, of course. I've probably been abused about 2,000 times already.
Yes, I know.
You understand, don't you?
Yes.
I thought, "Oh, I'm not going to put this in.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No matter how you think about it, it's not going in.
Oh no.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, yes, and for those who are watching the live broadcast, please do.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, my God!
Yes, yes.
It's kind of a, yes, it's kind of a personal matter, but I'm kind of grateful for it.
A personal matter?
It's nothing personal.
You don't have to talk about it if it's personal.
No, I'm sorry.
I knew it was just a sound effect.
No, it's not. No, it's not. No, it's not.
Yes, it is.
This is directly related to the "cold interior devils".
Yes.
Thankfully, on April 14, DNAVS Hanshin's, uh...
I was chosen for the urgent ceremony.
Wow.
It's me.
You're going to throw it?
Under the beach?
I'll throw it under the beach.
Wow.
It's big. Are you okay?
I'm fine!
Oh, no.
Have you ever played baseball before?
I've only played in class,
And this past week, well, a few weeks,
Well, there was a guy in my office who wanted to be a professional baseball player,
He taught me how to hold the ball.
That's good.
Yes, that's right. So, I'm thinking, "The day after tomorrow, I'm going to work a little harder,
The day after tomorrow, I'm going to have to work a little harder.
Okay.
I don't mean that I have to carry the program on my back, but...,
I'm not trying to carry the program, but they made uniforms in collaboration with DNA.
What?
That's right.
Like a "riyaa"?
A "riyaa". And a devil's mark here.
Wow.
That's right.
I'm not going to say this now, but..,
If you don't get a bounce or a strike,
I'll tell them it's okay to quit KanaeDevil.
Eeeee!
Wait a minute!
Oh no.
I'll do my best!
That's how you want it, isn't it?
No, but I'm sure of it.
Wow.
No, I'm really going to do my best.
Well, thank you very much for your support.
I'm looking forward to it. Uh, DNA versus?
Yes, half-body.
Tigers!
Wow!
That's a lot of people!
This is it!
I just had a meeting with them,
There must be 20,000 people there.
No, seriously, seriously, seriously.
I'm scared!
This is a very popular card.
No, it's true.
No, I'll do my best.
I'll be there to see you get beat up.
I'll come to the mound.
No, but I'm reassured.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
So, the day after tomorrow, then!
Yes, sir!
Are you okay?
I'll do my best!
I will see you for Hamas!
Thank you very much.
So, with that attitude, well, it's time to get back to you for the delivery as it is.
Yes, sir!
So, how was it?
From the Sobe family's point of view.
From the Sohbe family's point of view?
From the Sobue family's point of view?
From the Sobu family's point of view...
The Sobu family?
20,000 people...
The ceremony was a cat!The uterine ceremony was the cat!
The uterine ceremony is a cat.
Not a single word was spoken and 20,000 people were too surprised.
No, it's true.
No, I thought it was amazing.
I think there are more than 20,000 people.
That's right.
Good luck.
Do your best.
I'll do my best.
Please do your best.
Like that? Now.
No, no, no.
By all means, by all means.
Yes, yes, yes.
So that's how it is.
Well, I'll see you all next week for the live distribution.
Also, if you have time the day after tomorrow, by all means,
I would like you to come to the uterine ceremony.
Please come to the uterine ceremony.
And the other one in May?
Yes, that's right.
L.O.L...
L.O.L. Planets Shareholders' Meeting.
I think everyone at Kannami Hall will have time to attend.
So, with that said, Mr. Nakai, see you all later!
Thank you very much!
Yes, OK. Thank you very much.